wapbaze.com 2019-04-30

# Privacy Policy

We have created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices. **

Your Information is Private

**  
Subscribers are requested to enter limited personal information during signups. Under no circumstance will we sell, transfer or disseminate this personal information gathered by our products to any other entity. Google Analytics - Free Web Tracker and Counter

Our statistics product collects information about visitors to the subscriber's website. This information will also not be sold, transfered or disseminated to any other entity. We may display aggregated data to show industry trends (such as browser share). However, this data shall be the average of many thousands of sites and will in no way linked to individual subscribers.

**Cookie Usage**  
The use of cookies is limited to storing a small amount of non-identifiable information on a visitor's computer. For visitors to our sites, the data is used only to maintain information about the user's session.

For visitors to sites that have installed our statistics package, cookies are used to enhance the ability of our product to display usage patterns. This information does not in any way reveal any personal data about visitors. Visitors to a subscriber's site will receive a cookie that stores only a generic id, the prior page, time since last visit, and number of the visit.

**Access to Personal Account Data**  
Every subscriber is requested to enter limited personal information that is stored in our databases. This information may include credit card information for pay subscribers. At any time, subscribers may modify this information upon logging into the product using an account id and password. Credit card information is only requested on secure pages (using SSL 128-bit encryption). Credit card information is never re-displayed once entered.

**Opt-In E-Mail Lists**  
Every new subscriber has the option of not receiving site news and special promotional offers by either unchecking the opt-in check-box on the main signup form, or opting out of future mailings by clicking on the 'Opt-Out' link on any e-mail correspondance sent. Once an user opts-out no further e-mails will be sent except for traffic alerts the user sets up and important administrative notices.

**Children's Guidelines**  
This web site meets the guidelines of TRUSTe's Children's program, which means that it does:

1\. NOT collect online contact information without prior parental consent or parental notification, which will include an opportunity for the parent to prevent use of the information and participation in the activity. Without prior parental consent, online information will only be used to respond directly to the child's request and will not be used for other purposes without prior parental consent

2\. NOT collect personally identifiable offline contact information without prior parental consent

3\. NOT distribute to third parties any personally identifiable information with out prior parental consent

4\. NOT give the ability to publicly post or otherwise distribute personally identifiable contact information without prior parental consent

5\. NOT entice by the prospect of a special game, prize or other activity, to divulge more information than is needed to participate in the activity

**Contacting the Web Site**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact.  

**Our Google Policy For Wapbaze** Any advertisements served by Google, Inc., and affiliated companies may be controlled using cookies. These cookies allow Google to display ads based on your visits to this site and other sites that use Google advertising services. Learn how to opt out of Googles cookie usage. As mentioned above, any tracking done by Google through cookies and other mechanisms is subject to Googles own privacy policies. 

#### About Google advertising:

What is the DoubleClick DART cookie? The DoubleClick DART cookie is used by Google in the ads served on publisher websites displaying AdSense for content ads. When users visit an AdSense publisher's website and either view or click on an ad, a cookie may be dropped on that end user's browser. The data gathered from these cookies will be used to help AdSense publishers better serve and manage the ads on their site(s) and across the web. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

**Wapbaze** takes your privacy seriously. This privacy policy describes what personal information we collect and how we use it. See this [privacy policy primer](http://cybec.com/what-is-a-privacy-policy/) to learn more about privacy policies in general.

## Routine Information Collection

All web servers track basic information about their visitors. This information includes, but is not limited to, IP addresses, browser details, timestamps and referring pages. None of this information can personally identify specific visitors to this site. The information is tracked for routine administration and maintenance purposes.  

## Cookies and Web Beacons

Where necessary, wapbaze.com uses cookies to store information about a visitor's preferences and history in order to better serve the visitor and/or present the visitor with customized content.  
Advertising partners and other third parties may also use cookies, scripts and/or web beacons to track visitors to our site in order to display advertisements and other useful information. Such tracking is done directly by the third parties through their own servers and is subject to their own privacy policies. 

## Controlling Your Privacy

Note that you can change your browser settings to disable cookies if you have privacy concerns. Disabling cookies for all sites is not recommended as it may interfere with your use of some sites. The best option is to disable or enable cookies on a per-site basis. Consult your browser documentation for instructions on how to block cookies and other tracking mechanisms. This list of [web browser privacy management](http://cybec.com/web-browser-privacy-management/) links may also be useful.  

## Special Note About Google Advertising

Any advertisements served by Google, Inc., and affiliated companies may be controlled using cookies. These cookies allow Google to display ads based on your visits to this site and other sites that use Google advertising services. Learn how to [opt out of Google's cookie usage](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). As mentioned above, any tracking done by Google through cookies and other mechanisms is subject to Google's own privacy policies.   
**OUR DISCLAIMER** This our policy may be changed at any time in life at the discretion of Wapbaze. If we should update this policy, we will post the updates to this page on our Website only. This policy last updated on November 25th, 2014.
